Red
压制:随Feng
红色
Taylor Swift
歌手
爱他 如同驾驶着崭新的玛莎拉蒂冲进死路
Loving him is like driving a new Maserati down a dead end street
快如疾风 情深至罪 却也草草了结
Faster than the wind, passionate as sin, ending so suddenly
爱他 如同自由坠落之后试图回心转意
Loving him is like trying to change your mind once you're already flying through the free fall
好似秋色 纵使明艳 却将纷纷凋零
Like the colors in autumn, so bright, just before they lose it all
失去他 是蓝色 我从未知否
Losing him was blue, like I've never known
思念他 是深灰 我孑然一身
Missing him was dark grey, all alone
遗忘他 是将他当做陌生人重新来过
Forgetting him was like trying to know somebody you never met
而爱他 是红色
But loving him was red
烈焰般的红色
loving him was red
触碰他 如同美梦成真 尽现眼前
Touching him was like realizing All you ever wanted was right there in ront of you
铭记他 如同熟知最爱的老歌 字字句句
Memorizing him was as easy as knowing all the words to your old favorite song
与他争吵 如同竭力解开一道纵横字谜 却没有正确答案
Fighting with him was like trying to solve a crossword And realizing there's no right answer
对他抱歉 如同企望自己从来没有发觉 对他的爱是那么真切
Regretting him was like wishing you'd never found out that love could be that strong
失去他 是蓝色 我从未知否
Losing him was blue, like I've never known
思念他 是深灰 我孑然一身
Missing him was dark grey, all alone
遗忘他 是将他当做陌生人重新来过
Forgetting him was like trying to know somebody you never met
而爱他 是红色
But loving him was red
灼人的红色
Oh, red burning red
有关他的回忆排山倒海 不绝于耳
Remembering him comes in flashbacks, in echoes
告诉自己 该放手了
Tell myself it's time now, gotta let go
而当一切仍在脑海盘旋 怎可能将之弃于身后 毅然前行
But moving on from him is impossible when I still see it all in my head
灼人的红色
Burning red
爱他 是灼人的红色
Loving him was red
失去他 是蓝色 我从未知否
Losing him was blue, like I've never known
思念他 是深灰 我孑然一身
Missing him was dark grey, all alone
遗忘他 是将他当做陌生人重新来过
Forgetting him was like trying to know somebody you never met
只因爱他 是红色
Cause loving him was red
烈焰般的红
Yeah, yeah red
灼人的红色
burning red
就这样 他 萦绕脑海 挥散不去
And that's why he's spinning around in my head
如灼人的红色 向我涌来
Comes back to me, burning red
Yeah, yeah
对他的爱 如同驾驶着崭新的玛莎拉蒂 冲向不归路...
His love was like driving a new Maserati down a dead end street
压制:随Feng